coverlettersandresume.com 2019-02-27

# Privacy Policy | Cover Letters and Resume Samples

At coverlettersandresume.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by coverlettersandresume.com and how it is used.

  * We do not ask for your personal information unless we really need it (we will never ask for your personal or any kind of sensitive information).  

  * We don’t store any personal information on our servers unless you have given your consent for that.  

  * Our site uses technologies such as cookies to improve your user experience

 **Log Files**

Like many other websites, coverlettersandresume.com use log files. The information in the log files includes IP addresses, for example, to identify your general location, type of browser, Internet Service Provider, date/time stamp, entrance/referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits on coverlettersandresume.com.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to coverlettersandresume.com and/or other sites on the internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en).

For more information, please visit [Google Advertising Policies and Principles Page](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads), and [Partner Sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on coverlettersandresume.com send directly to your browsers.

They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

CoverLettersAndResume.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You can also consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of specific practices. coverlettersandresume.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

##  **Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

If you want to opt out from our Google Analytics reports, please visit [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/?hl=en).

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@coverlettersandresume.com.
